# COLM O'SULLIVAN

#### WEB DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

289-338-0510

colm.osullivan1@gmail.com

https://colmosullivan.ca/

github.com/ColmOSullivan

Toronto, ON, CA

# LANGUAGES& SKILLS

- React
- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- RESTful API
- JavaScript
- · Conflict Resolution
- · Problem solving

#### HOBBIES

- Magic: The Gathering
- Board games: Smallworld, Settlers of Catan, Condottiere.
- Reading: Malazan Book of the Fallen, Imperial Radch trilogy, The Three Body Problem, The Way of Kings
- Film: The Departed, Moonlight, Clerks
- Television: Fringe, 12 Monkeys, Aunty Donna

# EDUCATION

Certificate, Web Development Bootcamp

Juno College of Technology

August 2022 - November 2022

Certificate, Pre-apprenticeship Georgian College

May 2021 - January 2022

Diploma, Broadcasting and Film Centennial College

September 2009 - April 2012

#### PROFILE

I am an excellent communicator, analytical problem solver, and excited about empowering the world through technology.

With over ten years of experience in broadcast television, I have honed my abilities to communicate effectively, solve problems swiftly, and work efficiently within a team and independently.

#### **PROJECTS**

### **Flock of Friends**

HTML, Sass, JavaScript, React and, RESTful API 2022

## Free-to-play Game Generator

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and, RESTful API 2022

## **Who's That Pokemon Quiz**

HTML, Sass, JavaScript, and Restful API 2022

## **Under the Sea PSD Conversion**

HTML, Sass, and JavaScript 2022

\_\_\_\_\_

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Media Preparation Coordinator**

Rogers Sports & Media in Toronto

March 2021 - Present

- Support content distribution networks including web, broadcast news, entertainment, and sports
- Process content to ensue that they meet all technical requirements

#### **Automated Media Control Operator**

Bell Media in Toronto

December 2014-February 2021

- Ensured programming was consistent with expected schedules and guidelines
- Responsible for ensuring the on-air integrity of as many as twelve channels
- Communicated and coordinated with external departments and clients to meet competing deadlines, troubleshoot any technical difficulties

### **Master Control & Ingest Operator**

Astral Media in Toronto

January 2012 - November 2014

- Created non-linear content for internal departments and external clients.
- Digitized, ingested, and created database information related to all programming, promotional and commercial content